const QuizData = [
    {title: 'Math Quiz',
    content:[
        {
            question: "What is 6/2?",
            answerOptions: [ '3', '5', '15', '8',],
            correct: "3",
        },
        {
            question: "What is 10/2?",
            answerOptions: [ '3', '5', '15', '8',],
            correct: "5",
        },
        {
            question: "What is 30/3?",
            answerOptions: [ '3', '5', '10', '8',],
            correct: "10",
        }]
    },
    {title: 'Pokemon Quiz',
    content:[
        {
            question: "What does an Eevee evolve into if they're exposed to a Water Stone?",
            answerOptions: [ 'Jolteon', 'Flareon', 'Vaporeon', 'Espeon',],
            correct: "Vaporeon",
        },
        {
            question: "What does an Eevee evolve into if they're exposed to a Fire Stone?",
            answerOptions: [ 'Jolteon', 'Flareon', 'Vaporeon', 'Espeon',],
            correct: "Flareon",
        }]
    },
    {title: 'Katekyo Hitman Reborn Quiz',
    content:[
        {
            question: "Hibari has one weakness. What is it?",
            answerOptions: [ 'Canaries', 'Cherry Blossoms', 'Pineapples', 'Roses',],
            correct: "Cherry Blossoms",
        },
        {
            question: "Who is the leader of the Varia?",
            answerOptions: [ 'Squalo', 'Leviathan', 'Xanxus', 'Belphegor',],
            correct: "Xanxus",
        },
        {
            question: "The little canary bird that follows Hibari around has come to be known as what?",
            answerOptions: [ 'Tweety', "Hibari's bird", 'Cabari', 'Hibird',],
            correct: "Hibird",
        },
        {
            question: "Xanxus's box animal is made of wwhich two flame aspects?",
            answerOptions: [ 'Sky & rain', 'Sky & Lightning', 'Storm & Lightning', 'Sky & Storm',],
            correct: "Sky & Storm",
        },
        {
            question: "Knives and wire are whose main weapon?",
            answerOptions: [ 'Belphegor', 'Squalo', 'Leviathan', 'Lussuria',],
            correct: "Belphegor",
        }]
    },
    {title: 'Magic Quiz',
    content:[
        {
            question: "What's the name of the spell that unlocks doors?",
            answerOptions: [ 'Alchemy', 'Alohamora', 'Open Sesame', 'Apperate',],
            correct: "Alohamora",
        },
        {
            question: "What's the name of the spell that causes immense pain?",
            answerOptions: [ 'Crucio', 'Cruel', 'Inflicto', 'Incarcarous',],
            correct: "Crucio",
        },
        {
            question: "What's the name of the spell that stuns your opponent?",
            answerOptions: [ 'Impirium', 'Stupefy', 'Stunned', 'Silencio',],
            correct: "Stupefy",
        }]
    },
];

export default QuizData;